(Leonard:)So, what happens now?
(Lesley:)Well, I don't know about your sex drive,
but I'm probably good till New Year's.
(Penny:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Penny:)- Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You wanna make plans for New Year's?
- Please, you're smothering me.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Hey, look. It's Dr. Stud.
(Leonard:)Doctor what?
(Howard:)The blogosphere is abuzzing
with news of you and Leslie...
...making the bang, bang music.
- Well, how did it get on the Internet?
- I put it there.
(Leonard:)Well, how did you know about it?
(Raj:)A little bird told us.
(Raj:)Apparently, you are a magnificent beast.
(Leonard:)Well, that part's true.
(Sheldon:)I think I may have
misjudged this restaurant.
- No kidding.
- I don't wanna go out on a limb...